Guide to the Labor Publications and Printed Material Collection, "1861-2011 IBT0001
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Labor Publications and Printed Material Collection
1861-2013
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT0001
15.75 Linear Feet
The Labor Publications and Printed Material Collection is an artificial collection created by the Special Collections and University Archives from a variety of sources. This collection contains publications and printed materials related to labor organization in the United States. The material dates from 1861-2011. The collection consists of various materials published by union and non-union organizations. Significant topics include labor attitudes towards wages, civil rights, gender equality, and international cooperation.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains publications and printed materials related to labor organization in the United States. The material dates from 1861-2013. The collection consists of various materials published by union and non-union organizations. Significant topics include labor attitudes towards wages, civil rights, gender equality, and international cooperation.
Arrangement
Organized into 5 series: Business and Trade Associations, Government, Miscellaneous Labor, Reprints, Union Publications, and Oversized material.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transfered to Gelman Library, [(Accession Number)].
Biographical / Historical
The Labor Publications and Printed Material Collection is an artificial collection created by the Special Collections and University Archives from a variety of sources.
Politics and government; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions; Labor; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
- Business and Trade Associations, 1938-1959; Series 1; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically
  - The American Triange of Plenty by F. C. Crawford, 1943; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - An Analysis of the Ford Type Plan for Supplemental Unemployment Compensation by National Association of Manufacturers, undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Apprenticeship in the Metal Trades by National Metal Trades Association, 1959; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - A Better Understanding by Martins Ferry Division of Blaw-Know Company, undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Developments on the Labor-Management Front, 1954 December; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Drafting a Union Contract, 1965; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Employee's Pension Plan of United Wire and Supply Corporation by United Wire & Supply Corporation, 1956 October; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Employee Rating by National Metal Trades Association, 1942; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Employees' Supplemental Profit Sharing Plan by United Wire & Supply Corporation, 1959 May; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Grinding Wheel Care and Safety by Standard Safety Equipment Co., 1950 December 11; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Group Insurance Plan for Employees of Vermont Furniture Co. Inc. by Aetna Life Insurance Complany, undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Group Insurance Plan for Employees of Whitin Machine Works by Whitin Machine Works, 1959 April 1; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - A Guide to Preparing Employee Manuals by National Metal Trades Association, 1959; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Information for Employers Concerning the Social Security Act by Addressograph-Multigraph Corporation, 1935; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Interesting Information and Shop Rules for Yale & Towne Employees by Yale& Towne MFG. Co., 1938 February; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - ITF Research Book Globalising Solidarity, June 2002; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - ITF Research Book Responding to Liberalisation, January 2005; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - ITF Research Book Women Transporting the World, April 2002; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Job Rating Manual by National Metal Trades Association, undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Little Known Facts about America at Work by National Association of Manufacturers, 1941 January; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - N.M.T.A. Bulletins on Personnel Department Organization, Employment Application forms, Personnel Testing and Suggestion Systems by National Metal Trade Association, 1944-1958; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - The Men Who Make Steel by American Iron and Steel Institute, 1936 August; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Oil: Product and Pilar of Freedom by Eugene Holman, 1945 May; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Plan for Employees' Pension, Disability Benefits and Death Benefits by Southern New England Telephone Company, American Telephone and Telegraph Company and Associate and Allied Companies, 1940 January; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Public and Industrial Peace by National Association of Manufactures, 1946; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Questions and Answers about te Guaranteed Annual Wage by National Association of Manufactures, 1955 March; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Safety as it Applies to Supervisors by Marsh & McLennan, Inc., 1947; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - So You Don't Like Time Study Well...Who the Hell Does? by L.H. Woodman, the Daw Chemical Company, 1946; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Suggerstion System for Employees of the Bristol Plant by United States Rubber Co., undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - The Supervisor's Guide to the Taft-Hartley Act by National Foremen's Institute, 1947; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Thrift and Unemployment by the Committee on Industrial Relations, National Metal Trades Association, 1932; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Union Contract Clauses, 1954; Series 1 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Wage Incentive Practices by National Metal Trades Associated, 1959 May; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - When the Watchman Takes Over by Factory Insurance Association, undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Who, me...? Pointers on Job Management by Arthur O. England, 1954 April; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Government, 1935-1979; Series 2; 1 Linear Feet
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Administration of Child Labor Laws Part 1: Employment Certificate System Connecticut by Helen Sumner and Ethel Hanks, 1915; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Agreement Between the General Counsel of the National Labor Relations Board and the NLRB Professional Association, September 26, 1989; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Apprenticeship Past and Present by Unitedd States Department of Labor, Bureau of Apprenticeship, 1955; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration of Grievances, 1946; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - As Others See Us by Brookwood Building and Endowment Fund Drive, undated; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Brief History of the American Labor Movement by United States Department of Labor, 1957; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Cargo Ship Loading: An Analysis of General Cargo Loading in Selected U.S. Ports by National Academy of Sciences - National Research Council, 1957; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Causes of Labor and Unrest: Testimony of A.F. Whitney, President, Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, before Special Subcommittee of the Committee on Labor, U.S. House of Representatives, 1946 July 9; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Child Labor: A National Problem by National Child Labor Committee, 1914 May; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Child Labor Laws in All States by National Child Labor Committee, 1912 August; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement Between Food and Drug Administration, Department of Health and Human Services, and the National Treasury Employees Union, October 01, 1999; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Directory of National Unions and Employee Associations by U.S. Department of Labor, Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1979; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Effects of Mechanical Changes in the Cotton-Textile Industry 1910-1936 by Bureau of Labor Statistics, United States Department of Labor, 1937 August; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Essential Facts in Regard to the League of Nations, the World Court, and the International Labor Organization by Education Committee, the League of Nations Association, 1938 October; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Labor Laws and Agencies: A Guide for Shop Stewards and Supervisors by United States Department of Labor, Division of Labor Standards, 1946; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Federal Law and Agencies: A Guide for Shop Stewards by United States Department of Labor, Dividion of Labor Standards, 1946; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Hearings of the Committee of Governmental Affairs United States Senate, 1989, April, 04, 06, 12; IBT 0001 Series 2 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - How Owners of Homes and Business Property Can Secure the Benefit of the National Housing Act by Federal Housing Administration, undated; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - How to Boost Quality by Bureau of National Affairs, 1953; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - How to Get a Better Labor Agreement by Bureau of National Affairs, 1953; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - How to Get Teamwork by Bureau of National Affairs, 1953; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - The Humphrey-Hawkins Bill "Full Employment and Balanced Growth Act of 1977" (S.50 and H.R. 50) by Hubert H. Humphrey and Augustus F. Hawkins, 1977 January; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Important Events in American Labor History 1778-1968 by U.S. Department of Labor, Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Job Discrimination? Laws and Rules You Should Know by Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, undated; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Labor and Employment Law Desk Book, 1986; Series 2 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Letters About Taft Act, 1949-1966; IBT 0001 Series 2 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - New Labor Law of 1959 with Explanation "Labor Management Reporting and Disclosure Act of 1959", 1959 September 14; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Non-Communist Affidavits - California, 1948; IBT 0001 Series 2 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Personal Preparedness in the Nuclear Age by Department of Defense Office of Civil Defense, 1961 October; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Primer of Labor Relations by Labor Relations Reporter, Bureau of National Affairs, 1946; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Primer of Labor Relations: An Authentic Guide to Employer-Employee Conduct by Labor Relations reporter, Bureau of National Affairs, 1938; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Report on the Constitutionality of the National Labor Relations Act by National Commiittee of the American Liberty League, 1935 September 5; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Rules and Regulations Series 3, as amended and National Labor Relations Act by National Labor Relations Board, 1944 July 12; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Seminar on Manpower Policy and Program by Jack T. Conway and U.S. Department of Labor Manpower Administration, 1965 February; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Senate Report on the Relations between Labor and Capital, 1885; IBT0001 Series 2 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - State Workmen's Compensation Laws by United States Department of Labor, Bureau of Labor Standards, 1954 September; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Tenth Annual Conference, Federal Child Labor Bill, National Child Labor Committee, 1914 February; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Test Your Labor Know-How by Commerce Cleaning House Labor Law Reports and Commerce Clearing House Labor Arbitration Awards, 1961; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Testimony of A.F. Whitney and Charles Decker Before the President's Emergency Board, in Connection with Demands for a 30 percent Increase in Basic Rates, 1941 September 29; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Testimony of A.F. Whitney, President, Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen on Labor Relations Program Before the United States Senate Committee on Labor and Public Welfare, 1947 March 13; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - T.V.A. and You, undated; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - United Steelworkers of America V. United States of America, the Supreme Court of the United States, 1959 October; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, undated; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Wartime Care and Protection of Children of Employed Mothers before the Committee on Education and Labor United States Senate, 1943 June 8; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Victory Decisionof the United States Supreme Court in the Case of Angelo Herndon, decision of Justice Roberts, 1937 April; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Wartime Working Conditions: Minimum Standards for Maximum Production by United States Department of Labor Division of Labor Standards, 1943 September 1; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Where You Stand Under the Labor Reform Lawby Bureau of National Affairs, 1959; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Workmen's Compensation: The Workmen's Compensation Act as Amended in 1955 by Board of Commissioners, State of Connecticut, 1955 October 1; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Worker's Defense: Newsletter No. 2, 1979 January; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Miscellaneous Labor, 1861-2010; Series 3; 1 Linear Feet
  Arranged alphabetically. Note: starting with Box 16 the order of this series restarts.
  - African Liberation Movements: An Interim Bibliography compiled by Joseph Smaldone, 1974; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - African Workers and Apartheid by David Davis, March 1978; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - The Agent Provacateur in the Labor Movement by Johannes Buchner, undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - The Art of Railroading, 1905; IBT0001 Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Automation: It's Impact on Business and Labor by John Diebold, 1959 May; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Behind Bars for the First Amendment, 1960 March; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Biddle's Private War Against Harry Bridges, undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - The British Strike: It's Background --- It's Lessons by William F. Dunnes, 1928 October 16; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Black Workers Set the Pace by Jim Jacobs, 1969 April; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - The Burning Question of Russian Oil by W.P. Coates, 1927 October; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - California Rural Legal Assistance 1966-1986: Celebrating Twenty Years of Legal Services", Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Can Labor and Management Work Together? by Osgood Nichols and T.R. Carskadon, 1949; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Canals and Industry: Engineering in Lowell, 1821-1880 by Patrick M. Malone, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Capital and Labor: A Fair Deal by Otto H. Kahn, 1919 April 24; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Chez des Amis en Afrique Libre by Gunter Schabowski, 1960; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - The Chicago Strike of 1894: Industrial Labor in the Nineteen century by Thomas G. Manning, 1960; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Chicago's Strike Ordeal by Stanley Powers, 1903; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Christianity on the Nazi Cross by the Labor Chest for Relief and Liberation of Workers of Europe, undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - The CIA and the Labour Movement by Fred Hirsch, 1977; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - The Closing Argument of W.E. Boragh for the Prosecution, in the Great Coeur D'Alene Riot-Murder Trial, Delivered July 27, 1899, Wallace Idaho", undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Commonweal, February 17, 1967; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Conference of Independent African States-Accra, Ghana, April 1958; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - La Conference de Casablanca, January 1961; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Constitutional Action for Peace by William Lloyd, Jr., 1947; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Corporate Shadow Boards by Americans Concerned About Corporate Power, 1980 April 7; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - The Day Will Come...Stories of the Haymarket Martyrs and the Men and Women Buried Alongside the Monument, 1994; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Discrimination at Waiters Local no. 17 Los Angeles by Vanguard Society of America, 1960 March; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - East Africa Journal, November 1964-August 1965; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - An Economic Framework For Aviation in Latic America, n.d.; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - The Elements of Railroad Engineering, 1897; IBT 0001 Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Employee Involvement national Joint Committee On Employee Involvement, n.d.; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Equality and Efficiency: The Big Tradeoff by Arthur M. Okun, 1975; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Fabric of Injustice: The Struggle at J.R. Stevens by National Council of the Churches of Christ in the U.S.A., 1977 November; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Fascism in the United States by Kenneth Patton, 1953; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Freedom, Inequality, Primitivism, and the Division of Labor by Murray Rothbard, 1971; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Fuel Economy on Locomotives by American Railway Master Mechanics' Association, 1915 October 15; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Get Out if You Can: The Saga of Sal si Puedes, 1953; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - The Grievance: Poems from the Shop Floor by Martin Glaberman, 1980; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - The Great Lumber Strike orf Humbolt County 1935 by Frank Onstine, 1979 November12; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - How to Avoid a Lawsuit, 1952; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - How to Make the Most Out of Your Job by H.K. Dugdale, 1955; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - How Vanzetti Said Goodbye, 1982; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - The Impact of Neo-Liberal Globalisation on Women Transport Workers, 19-20 April 2004; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - The Injunction Against Brookwood, 1928; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - An Introduction to Labor Laws by Michael Evan Gold, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Job Classifications, 1962 August 25; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Journal of Modern African Studies, 1966; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - The Kremlin and Labor: A Study in National Security Policy" by Roy Godson, 1977; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Labor and the Cold War by Stewart Meacham, 1959 September; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Labor Costs and International Trade by N. Arnold Tolles and Bett C. Goldwasser, 1961; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Labor Exchange Note, 1897; IBT0001 Series 3 (Box SHARED Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Labor Heroines: The Women Who Led the Struggle by Joyce Maupin, 1974; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Labor History Documents Volume I, 1974; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Labor History Documents Volume II, 1974; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Labor Law Journal, September 1953; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Labor Law Journal, July 1976; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - The Labor Movement in the United States by Jack Barbash, 1958; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Labor's Non-Partisan League: It's Origin and Growth by Labor's Non-Partisan League, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - The Labor-Value Fallacy by The Patriots' League, 1887; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Labor vs. Apartheid - The Struggle in One by U.S. Peace Council, 1986 February; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Landon's Platform, Roosevelt's Record by Daniel J. Tobin, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Le Mouvement Syndical Ouest Africain d'Expression Francaise, 1965; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Letter to Members by The Employer's Association of Greater Chicago, 1959 September 18; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Lip and the Self-Managed Counter-Revolution by Black & Red, 1975; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Little Journeys to Homes of Reformers by Elbert Hubbard, by Henry George, 1907; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Mississippi's First Labor Union by Ken Lawrence, 1974; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - "NACLA's Latin America and Empire Report: Hit and Run: U.S. Runaway Shops on the Mexican Border", 1975 July; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Negotiating Labor-Management Contracts by Donald E. Cullen, 1965 September; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - The Next Generation: A Handbook for Mentoring Future Union Leaders, 2012; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Nigeria Report-U.S. House Committee on Foreign Affairs (H.Res 143), March 12, 1969; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Norwegian Labor Looks at...the United States of America and the Union of Soviet Socialist Republics by Norwegian National Trafe Union Delegations, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Oil for the World by Standard Oil Company (New Jersey), undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Our Company Our Contract, n.d.; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Pan-Africanism in Action: An Account of the UAM by Albert Tevoedjre, 1965; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - PanAfricanism and the African Trade Union Movement, November 1959-September 1963; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Peace by Finesse by J.W. Still, 1965; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Perspectives On Work, 2012; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Popular Booklets For Members and Organizing Drives, 2002-2003; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - The Practical Chart and Handbook of Parliamentary Motions by Byrle A. Whitney, 1923; IBT 0001 Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Pride at Work: Organizing for Lesbian and Gay Rights in Unions by Miriam Frank and Desma Holocomb, 1990; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Public Speaking: A Speaker's Guide Book by Peter Cacchione, undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Q. What's Happening to Our Jobs? by Steve Babson, Nancy Brigham and Popular Economics Press, 1976; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - "Relations Industrielles" articles by Leon A. Dale, Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - A Report to the Fund for the Republic: Union Constitutions by Leo Bromwhich, 1959; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Reservoir Filling Station, 1932; IBT 0001 Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Resolution of the National Negro Congress, 1936 February 14-16; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Service On The Ground: Occupational Health of Ariport Check-In Workers, 2003; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - The Shame That Is Kentucky's! The Story of the Harlan Mine War by E.J. Costello, undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - The Sharonville Story, January 1983; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Sit Down by Joel Seidman, 1937; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Social Stratification in the United States: An Analytical Guidebook by Stephen Rose, 1979; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Socialism as an Incubus on the American Labor Movement by J.W. Sullivan and Hayes Robbins, 1918; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Statement by the AFL-CIO Executive Council on the AFL-CIO and the ICFTU, May 14, 1969; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Statement by George G. Kidwell in Answer to Charges Preferred Against Him by Certain Delegates to the San Francisco Labor Council, 1939 May 19; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Steadfast Activist at 84 by Corliss Lamont, 1986; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Still More About Brookwood College, undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Third Annual John H. Fanning Conference on Labor-Management Relations by Quirk Institute of Industrial Relations, 1978 April 7; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - This Was Trucking, 1966; Series 3 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - The Tobacco Worker, 1907, January; IBT0001 Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Trade Unions and Democracy by National Planning Association, 1957 October; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - UAW-Ford Joint Programs, 2012; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Unemployment: The Wolf at the Door by Art Shields, 1958 December; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Union Committeemen and Wildcat Strikes, 1971; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Union Town: A Labor History Guide to Detroit, 1979; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Vote CIO...and Get a Soviet America by Joseph P. Kamp, 1944; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Wages Book of the Glad Tidings from Liverpool, IBT 0001 Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 5)